<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<file>
   <object title="crashReporter">
      <methods>
         <method name="start">
            <param name="options" type="Object">
               <property optional="true" name="companyName" type="String"/>
               <property name="submitURL" type="String">
                  <description>
                     <para>URL that crash reports will be sent to as POST.</para>
                  </description>
               </property>
               <property optional="true" name="productName" type="String">
                  <description>
                     <para>Defaults to app.getName().</para>
                  </description>
               </property>
               <property optional="true" name="uploadToServer" type="Boolean">
                  <description>
                     <para>Whether crash reports should be sent to the server Default is true.</para>
                  </description>
               </property>
               <property optional="true" name="ignoreSystemCrashHandler" type="Boolean">
                  <description>
                     <para>Default is false.</para>
                  </description>
               </property>
               <property optional="true" name="extra" type="Object">
                  <description>
                     <para>An object you can define that will be sent along with the report. Only string properties are sent correctly. Nested objects are not supported.</para>
                  </description>
               </property>
            </param>
            <description>
               <para>You are required to call this method before using any other crashReporter APIs and in each process (main/renderer) from which you want to collect crash reports. You can pass different options to crashReporter.start when calling from different processes.</para>
               <para>Note Child processes created via the child_process module will not have access to the Electron modules. Therefore, to collect crash reports from them, use process.crashReporter.start instead. Pass the same options as above along with an additional one called crashesDirectory that should point to a directory to store the crash reports temporarily. You can test this out by calling process.crash() to crash the child process.</para>
               <para>Note: To collect crash reports from child process in Windows, you need to add this extra code as well. This will start the process that will monitor and send the crash reports. Replace submitURL, productName and crashesDirectory with appropriate values.</para>
               <para>Note: If you need send additional/updated extra parameters after your first call start you can call setExtraParameter on macOS or call start again with the new/updated extra parameters on Linux and Windows.</para>
               <programlisting>
 const args = [
   `--reporter-url=${submitURL}`,
   `--application-name=${productName}`,
   `--crashes-directory=${crashesDirectory}`
 ]
 const env = {
   ELECTRON_INTERNAL_CRASH_SERVICE: 1
 }
 spawn(process.execPath, args, {
   env: env,
   detached: true
 })
</programlisting>
               <para>Note: On macOS, Electron uses a new crashpad client for crash collection and reporting. If you want to enable crash reporting, initializing crashpad from the main process using crashReporter.start is required regardless of which process you want to collect crashes from. Once initialized this way, the crashpad handler collects crashes from all processes. You still have to call crashReporter.start from the renderer or child process, otherwise crashes from them will get reported without companyName, productName or any of the extra information.</para>
            </description>
         </method>
         <method name="getLastCrashReport">
            <returns type="CrashReport"/>
         </method>
         <method name="getUploadedReports">
            <returns type="CrashReport" isArray="true"/>
         </method>
         <method name="getUploadToServer">
            <returns type="Boolean">
               <description>
                  <para>Whether reports should be submitted to the server. Set through the start method or setUploadToServer.</para>
               </description>
            </returns>
            <description>
               <para>Note: This API can only be called from the main process.</para>
            </description>
         </method>
         <method name="setUploadToServer">
            <param name="uploadToServer" type="Boolean">
               <description>
                  <para>Whether reports should be submitted to the server</para>
               </description>
            </param>
            <description>
               <para>This would normally be controlled by user preferences. This has no effect if called before start is called.</para>
               <para>Note: This API can only be called from the main process.</para>
            </description>
         </method>
         <method name="setExtraParameter">
            <param name="key" type="String">
               <description>
                  <para>Parameter key.</para>
               </description>
            </param>
            <param name="value" type="String">
               <description>
                  <para>Parameter value. Specifying null or undefined will remove the key from the extra parameters.</para>
               </description>
            </param>
            <description>
               <para>Set an extra parameter to set be sent with the crash report. The values specified here will be sent in addition to any values set via the extra option when start was called. This API is only available on macOS, if you need to add/update extra parameters on Linux and Windows after your first call to start you can call start again with the updated extra options.</para>
            </description>
         </method>
      </methods>
   </object>
</file>
